

# **SKILLS**

LARAVEL / PHP

HTML / CSS

JAVASCRIPT / JQUERY

WORDPRESS

CDR/PSD

# HOBBIES



**TRAVEL** 



**MUSIC** 



MOVIE



**SPORT** 

### CONTACT





PATEL VADI - 8 JAMNAGAR



MRJESS.IN



MR.JASMIN.SHUKAL@GMAIL.COM



#### **ABOUT ME**

My name is Jasmin Shukla. I'm born and broth up in Jamnagar. My role model is my father . I belongs to Jamnagar , Gujarat ( India ) . I have completed my Graduation in BCA (Bachelor of Computer Application) from Saurashtra university Rajkot. My long term goal is to become more responsible and knowledgeable personality, on respected position in a company. I have 5 years of experience working with computer technology . I have a bachelor's degree in bca. I consider myself a good public speaker, and I have a good sense of humor.



## **EDUCATION**

**HSC(HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE)** 2011 - 2012

> **GUJARAT SECONDARY AND HIGHER ONDARY EDUCATION BOARD**

**GUJRAT, INDIA** 

**COMPUTER OPERATOR &** 2013 - 2016 **PROGRAMMING ASSISTANT** 

> INDUSTRIAL TRANING INSTITUTE **GUJARAT, INDIA**

2016 - 2018

**BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION** 

SAURASHTRA UNIVERSITY - RAJKOT **GUJARAT, INDIA** 



#### **EXPERIENCE**

2018 - TILL **SMART-WEBTECH** 

> GURUDWARA CHOWKDI, JAMNAGAR GUJARAT INDIA

2018 - 2018 **BINARY BITS** 

> KHODIYAR COLONY. JAMNAGAR GUJARAT INDIA

2017 - 2018 **RAJ DESIGN** 

INDRAPARAST,

JAMNAGAR GUJARAT INDIA

2016 - 2017 PHOTOGRAPHY DESIGNER

> SHREE ART DIGITAL STUDIO JAMNAGAR GUJARAT INDIA



## ACADMIC PROJECT

6 TH SEM BCA **ONLINE CLOTH SHOPING** ASP.NET

5 TH SEM BCA **ONLINE POLICE COMPLAINT** PHP

2 TH SEM ITI **AMARNATH BOARD** HTML/CSS